It never begins. And
thus. it never ends.
What's wrong?
- Is that not all of it?
- Too much of it.
Garmen?
- Garmen?
- No. no.
- Not now. I told you...
- Every minute we do nothing.
we look weak. We
look confused. right?
The people. Our people. The community.
they're looking for answers.
Cops. they're gonna
let this shit go.
- So. what do we do?
- Aked. it's up to your auntie.
- You know that. right?
- She's not telling me nothing. though.
Look. I love her. but this...
- It's family. It's my family.
- All right.
Ms. Mahabir. my condolences.
I'm sorry. ma'am.
- I'm going back home for a few days.
- Home to Georgetown?
- Back to Guyana. Why?
- To get some answers.
Auntie. we have all the answers.
- Edward Chung killed your brother-in-law.
- Aked. this isn't about Edward Chung.
This is about something that
happened a long. long time ago.
And I am going to get some
guidance on exactly how to respond.
And believe me. I will respond.
And when I do. I promise
you'll be a part.
- A big part.
- A big part. I promise that.
"A long time ago." how?
Yeah. I don't know.
You're right to
believe the bad things
happening to your family
are happening for a reason.
But I found the man responsible
for your misfortune.
and he's willing to allow you
to reverse your family's fate.
But you must be willing
to take certain steps.
exactly as he prescribes them.
- Are you willing?
- I am.
You understand that to balance
the weight of his pain.
to close the circle
of his own suffering.
suffering which
began many years ago
at the hand of your
late husband. Ranwell.
you will have to inflict a
similar pain on his behalf.
- I know.
- Okay. then.
Here is where we begin.
- Jared. honey. it's quarter of.
- I know.
Is there anything I can
do to help? 'Cause...
- No. I'm coming.
- You didn't touch the avocado toast.
I don't want you getting
starved by second period
and eating from the
vending machine.
Mom. I ate earlier. It was that
Indian food from last night.
Have you seen my cleats?
They're in the new closet
with the outside shoes.
I have to say. I was kinda surprised to
see that pitch meeting on the schedule.
- We know we're gonna say no.
- No. we don't know that. And anyway.
sometimes knowing why we're
saying no can be good too.
Here's an idea. how about
your dad actually takes
one of these meetings himself?
You mean do the
work part of work?
He did not eat that Indian food.
Okay. I'm putting your food and a
water. drink it. in your backpack.
And bring home the
Tupperware. okay?
I'm picking you up after
school. bud. Don't run off.
Dad. I know.
All right. if you're gonna
get the bus. we gotta move.
We pay a generous upfront fee to
license his name and likeness.
and all we'd ask is maybe once a year.
he gives us an appearance or two.
Plus. Chef Jeff and his family
will always have a free room.
Whether it's Atlantic City.
Las Vegas.
or the big wow. Macau.
- Be in touch.
- Yeah.
See? It's good to do
sometimes. these meetings.
- So. what...
- Jacket copy. blurbs.
and the publisher still needs you
guys to approve the cover image.
- Okay.
- And they wanna know.
- is he keeping the ponytail?
- I'm gonna let you handle that.
Remember. all you
need to do is...
I know. I just... I need to
play nice and don't interrupt.
Exactly. Just state your case. 'Cause
it's a good one. They need you.
They should have put
you on this a year ago.
Yeah. I would have
turned somebody by now.
Then my job wouldn't be
on the chopping block.
- So...
- So. I know.
I need to just stay present.
not talk about the past.
I will be the model
of obedient servitude.
And he will never know how much I
think he's a backstabbing weasel
- who would sell out his own mother to...
- Mel. Mel. Nice face.
Right. Nice face.
Why don't you admit why you
really want on the case?
Pete Fong has to trim
the department budget.
you think you're vulnerable 'cause
you're low man on the pole. but...
we both know that's not the reason
why you're vulnerable. is it?
Maybe you actually really
don't wanna put me on the case
because it's stalling
and you know that I would
actually do something with it.
which would make you look bad.
and then it would be
impossible for you to fire me
which is what you really wanna
do if you're being honest. right?
Well. if I'm being honest...
you're kind of impossible
to deal with. Mel.
I mean. case in point.
antagonizing your boss
as you're asking for
a favor... again.
Again?
Last year... when I risked my fucking
job by not turning in your psych eval?
- Remember that?
- Manny.
Yeah. Yeah. You asked real nice.
- Without fucking insults.
- Okay. Okay.
I'm sorry. And I get it. You're
right. I appreciate it. okay?
But I don't want to relitigate the
past. I'm talking about my future.
Which is me working on
the Guyana case. okay?
- Not gonna happen. Mel.
- Manny!
- Go back to the Queen's College thing.
- Oh. my God!
You were supposed to
turn it in two weeks ago.
Right. Yes. You're right.
Because that massive
criminal organization
led by a dorm kid mailing fucking
fake IDs to high schoolers
is endangering more lives
than actual gangsters murdering bums
and vagrants for insurance premiums.
Oh. I'm sorry. Is the assignment
not sexy enough for you?
Here's a fact.
When you have a job. you get
assignments from your boss.
I'm your boss. You don't do
the fucking assignment...
- Manny.
- You get fired.
Don't get fired. Mel.
Damn it.
- Well?
- So. I'm working the Guyana case.
Oh. my God! Well done.
you. So he agreed with you.
No.
So he didn't actually
put you on the case?
- No. No. He didn't. No.
- But you said you're gonna work it.
Yeah. On my own time.
- Oh. Mel.
- Yeah.
Next one. Ready?
Here we go. Square up.
That's... not bad. Two hands.
Just watch it all
the way to the glove.
Here we go.
Here we go. Get it.
Get on your horse!
That was my bad. Good hustle.
What? Seriously? He
lost his phone again?
- You looked everywhere? Behind the dugout?
- Yes. Dad.
- Under the bench?
- I said yes.
It was in my shoes.
Yup. He sure did.
- Really?
- You saw me take them off.
You saw me never go back in the
dugout. I don't know how it happened.
You heard correctly.
Yeah. we'll give him
the talk. Part Seven.
- Hey.
How'd it go with the
proofs? Pick a winner?
Well. they're all winners.
So where did we land with
the whole losing stuff thing?
I told him this time
there's no new one.
- You heard that. right. bud?
- Yes.
Did you do Find My iPhone?
The phone has to be on to track
it. I'm sure they wiped it anyways.
Are you sure? 'Cause you
were sure four months ago
when you lost the watch
that Grandpa Jeff gave you.
Grandpa's watch? You lost it?
W... How did I not know this?
And the sweatshirt. His favorite
one. The one he waited in line for
then had to spend four
months allowance to replace.
- Where are you going?
- Find My iPhone. again.
Just tell me when
dinner's ready.
- I am not finished.
- Derek. just let him...
Moving forward. Jared.
buddy. help us out here.
Huh? What is the plan?
What kind of systems are
we gonna put in place
- so this all stops?
- I don't know.
How about one where I don't
somehow lose everything?
I need two boys.
Preferably from GT.
What kind of time frame
are we talking. Ms. M?
- As soon as possible.
- Why Georgetown?
We probably got people here
who can do whatever you want.
No. Garmen. I want people
who will do what we say
and won't ask questions.
Natalia. the masseuse. she have a
brother who got into trouble in GT.
He want to come up with his
best friend. Let's arrange it.
Yo!
- Xavier.
- Louis.
- What's going on? Look. look.
- Now?
Bye. everybody. Bye.
Oh. Louis!
- So. this is really happen?
- Yeah. man.
You get the passport?
So. when we at the forest
across the river...
- Raas.
- They will give it to us
then take us to the airport.
Hey. Shakeela. It's me. Xavier.
Me buddy come through.
I know. I know.
I don't know. His sister
arrange everything.
Me and you. we go meet
in person. finally.
Ticketing.
You know. I've gotta see this
for a very. very. very long time.
Long time. Long time.
Let's go.
- Kingston to Georgetown. brother.
- Yeah. man. And now New York!
Yeah. yeah. yeah! New York!
- Yeah. man.
- Crazy.
Hey. hey. Shakeela. It's me. Xavier.
I can't wait to see you in person.
We got a little meeting first.
but let me know what time school finish
and text me a place you want meet.
Louis. your sister
waiting for you.
She'll take you both straight
to your meeting with Aked.
Little gift to get you started.
Thank you. Mr. Len.
- Thank you. sir.
- Thank Mrs. Mahabir. It's from her.
And I need your passports.
Okay.
Hey. Xav.
Let me be straight with you.
Us coming here wasn't
my sister's idea.
You told me she
arrange everything.
No. Natalia boss
My sister may not be
too happy to see us.
Just warning you.
And you're just
telling me this now?
Yeah.
I hear you was running weed. Louis.
which means you lied to me on the phone.
We was just tricked. Nat.
Point was I gonna be
sending you money this time.
Point is. I hope you happy 'cause
now you into something different.
Ain't even a hello? Hey!
You'll get one when
I'm done being mad.
This Xavier. Friend
I tell you about.
He from upriver too.
My sister. Natalia.
- Me auntie friends with your mother.
- I know you.
In our primary school
you stole my kickball.
Probably. I don't know.
Well. Xavier. you got
legs. You can follow too.
Let's go. You coming or not? Now
ain't the time to keep Aked waiting.
The thing about Garmen
Harry. Number one. loyalty.
Number two. loyalty.
And number three...
What's number three?
What was... Loyalty.
All right?
Is Garmen the boss?
Garmen "Mr. Harry" to you.
The boss is Mrs. Mahabir.
Or if and only if she gives
you permission. Ms. M.
Full disclosure. Savitri
Mahabir is my aunt.
So. you wanna talk
to her? Through me.
Ask Nat.
I don't do this
for nobody. Nobody.
But she vouches for
you. baby brother.
You...
I don't know about.
But what you say is
true they gonna use you.
How much they pay?
Place to stay. lawyers
for a Green Card.
and you must be forgetting
they paid for your travel.
but I'm gonna let that slide.
You work it off.
- Sky the limit.
- How much I work off?
- About 50K per. something like that.
- U.S.?
U.S.? I like this guy. You funny.
Yeah. yeah. U.S. We're here now. baby.
Sometime few weeks from now. a guy.
Paul. is gonna assign you a trial.
Savitri Mahabir. Garmen Harry.
Paul Tranquada. me...
you.
You guys are good?
Yeah? You know
what you're doing?
All right. You can't miss him.
He's in a wheelchair. If
he's awake. he's talking.
I hope you boys appreciate the
nature of this opportunity.
- Yes. sir.
- Yeah?
- Thank you. sir.
- Yeah.
- Thank you. Mr. Paul. sir.
- You're welcome.
All right. You guys can go.
No. no. no. no. man. The
plastic is in the atmosphere
'cause the damn astronauts keep
throwing the shit out of window.
I mean. we got plastic in our
blood now. 'Cause of NASA.
Yeah. yeah. It's in a
book. I read all the books.
I read 'em all. You see?
The books are the truth.
I know that the only way
you can tell the truth
is to put it in a book.
And everybody else knows
that. You see what I'm saying?
How do you know that?
Because ink cost money.
Fucking wasting my time
around stupid-ass shit.
I'm a book reader. I read
books. That's what I do.
They mad at me
because I know stuff.
Hey. brother. we get
something for you.
Yo. what the fuck?
Yo. who are you. man?
Quiet down. man.
Yo. what you doing? No.
no. I'm good. I'm good.
- Relax yourself.
- You can stop here. I'm good.
I just get a little
present for you.
Yo. who are you with. man?
- Are you with Paul?
- Just a friend. All right?
- No. no. no. I'm asking. Wait.
- Keep your voice down.
- What are you doing. man?
- Shut your mouth.
What are you... No. stop.
How you... No. no. no.
No. no. No. no. I don't
want nothing. I'm clean.
- It's gonna be all right.
- No. I swear. I'm good. man.
I'm good. No. I'm sorry.
Come on. please. No.
What are you doing?
- Come on! Move! Help me. man.
- No. no. please. Stop.
- Help. man!
- Hey. man. Help me. man.
- Come on.
- Quiet. man. Relax yourself.
Quiet yourself. Sorry.
Move! Move now. man.
Natalia. Did you know
they would do that?
You did know?
They might make it look like an
accident. But it ain't no accident.
He raas dead now.
Nat. That scunt.
I've been trying
to get out. Louis.
- Shit.
- I been trying.
Oh. shit.
I'm at massage school
two nights a week.
I got janitorial at the massage
school five nights a week.
I got Ms. Mahabir during the
day. so I can pay her off.
Almost done too.
Every time one of them dead.
Natalia. you are part of it.
The new boys were the ones
that pull it off with Neilsen?
The two of them. One
better than the other.
but with Neilsen's drug history. they
could pass this one through fast.
We anticipating a payout
for the full policy.
Three hundred and
twenty-five thousand dollars.
- That's good. Well done.
- But that not come until next year.
We got some bigger
issues this year.
especially when I trying to reconcile
the financial mess Quincy left us in
- after he died...
- Look. Garmen. Garmen.
Let's focus forward.
You mean. for this next thing
you get? Whatever it is.
- Coming down the pike.
- That one. Yes.
Well. how am I gonna know unless
you tell me what that thing is.
It's the most important
thing we've ever done.
It involves a boy.
But I don't want to say no more
because me nah wan blight de ting.
So. you're scared me will jinx
it and give you a bad eye.
but I can't run it unless
you tell me what it is.
You're not gonna
run it. Aked is.
Ma'am.
You say it's the
most important thing.
It's also the most dangerous.
And this way you can supervise.
stay safe and help Aked.
Try not to kill himself.
Natalia. I told you this was gonna be big.
This is huge. So. what's your problem?
Why is kidnapping some pickney gonna
make up for what happened to Quincy?
- Reasons.
- Reasons?
- Yes. Reasons.
- Aked.
From the boss.
Who's grieving right
now. You know that.
Look. my auntie
left me in charge.
All right? Me in charge of
all this. You understand?
Version six.
I like this one.
Leave notes. Okay?
So. you know. like.
Chef Jeff or whoever. the
kid's father. whatever.
They pull up to the
library. boom. next place.
Subway station. I don't
know. I'm making it up.
Boom. They get to the
library. open up an envelope.
"Congratulations. you
made it to the library."
"Now. you got to book
it to the bridge."
Gonna keep it clever.
So yeah. Yeah. Shakeela.
It's me. Xavier.
So yeah. I was thinking
maybe we could do that again.
Maybe nighttime this time.
Or. you know.
maybe even tonight?
I just going for a walk now. so
if you done all your homework
and you feel like
catching a vibe just.
yeah. just give me a call.
But...
Yeah. I'ma call you right back.
You didn't happen
to be in the alley
behind Gemini's Lounge
the other night. did you?
Is... this familiar to you? You
know. dead body. wheelchair.
We brought the sheet.
- No idea.
- Oh. you know. I wonder
if I described the alley to
you. if it will jog your memory.
So. we have Gemini's Lounge.
next to the laundromat.
next to the pawn shop.
which. like all pawn shops.
has a security camera. which as you
know. have gotten very good these days.
- Let me see that.
- I... Sorry. It's government property.
However. my name is on this.
And whenever you're ready to
give me yours. give me a call?
It will happen in Washington Square
Park at 1:11 a.m.. inside a circle.
We will be in the park
to make sure there is no
deviation from the plan.
He will feel the same pain I
felt when I lost my grandson.
A boy for a boy.
And the balance will be
restored and all will be good.
It will.
Well. I want to hear
from Mr. Joseph directly.
Everything will be good.
Excellent. excellent.
Thank you. gentleman.
- Thank you. It was an honor. madam.
- The honor was all mine. I assure you.
We'll see you tomorrow
night at the celebration.
Yes. Tomorrow we
shall celebrate.
- I'll be right there. Natalia.
- Yes. Ms. Mahabir.
Natalia. is
everything all right?
Yes. Ms. Mahabir.
- Good night. sir.
- Good night.
Xavier. I need you to go
to Washington Square Park.
Lower Manhattan. You can Google
it. Ms. Mahabir asking for...
Apparently. there are... circles
in the park in different places.
She want to know the various
sizes. where. how many...
Yeah. My advice to you. Xavier.
watch your ass on this one.
Good night. sir.
Okay.
I just don't feel like four people talking
in a room for two hours is a movie.
Okay. I just
thought you'd be mad
that I brought you to a
movie where you had to read.
Yeah. I mean. that didn't help.
Oh. shit. Hold on.
Inspector Harmony speaking.
Who might this be?
My name is Xavier.
If I give you information.
can you get me home?
Home. home. home? Like Guyana?
- Yes.
- No.
But I can try to
make your life easier
in direct proportion to
the information given.
Divided by. of course. how
seriously you've already
fucked your life.
Something is going
down tomorrow night.
Well. that's a good first step.
Second step. where is it happening?
Washington Square Park.
It's four in the morning.
Why are you waking me up?
They gonna kill that boy.
The one they kidnapping. I
heard Mrs. Mahabir say it.
No matter what happen.
she want to kill him.
Why?
She think it some kind of answer to
all the bad that's been happening.
- How that make sense?
- She crazy. is how.
All of sudden. nothing
she do makes sense.
She bring these people
here from Guyana last week
and got a whole plan.
And he picked Xavier for the plan.
but I just told him you'd be good too
- because he may need one more person...
- You put me up for that?
- Quiet! Quiet.
- You all upset about it then you put me
- up for it? This is exactly what...
- Louis. I got a plan.
- I don't want to do.
- Louis!
You ain't gonna kidnap the boy.
You're gonna save him.
We gonna.
What?
- Why?
- Because you said it...
If someone dead.
I'm a part of it.
I'm trying to do
the right thing.
- And you should be too.
- Natalia. Natalia!
The thing that's happening...
when that gonna happen?
Aked was worried if he put
a crew together too soon.
they'd talk so we just
know telling Xavier...
Natalia. When this a happening?
Tonight.
Muddaskunt.
Tonight? And you're just
telling me this now?
I had to wait 'till
Aked fell asleep.
I don't know how we
gonna do all of it.
gonna do most of it.
But I know how we
at least can start.
I'm texting you where
to go to get the bike.
It's got to be the exact
laundry bike that Aked is using.
You see the photo here. Okay?
And I need you to
get this black bag.
I'm texting it now to you. Okay?
And get a wig. Any type of wig.
Okay. Now. I'm sending you a address
I need you to leave the bike.
I go get it after work. I
go put the dummy inside.
All right? I need you to text me when
you get close to the park. All right?
So. which one of my
plans we going with?
The one where you wait for
us to tell you what to do.
- When is that?
- When we tell you.
They've gotten super controlling.
They won't even let me lock my phone.
They're trying to prove a point
about me being responsible.
Plus. I can't go out
anyway. I've got tutor.
What if I promise
it'll be worth it?
Like... I can tell you what
happened to your stuff.
It's a business transaction.
I'll tell you more about it
in the van. Okay? Come on.
How is grabbing a little
boy a business transaction?
I said I'd tell you more
about it in the van.
You good. Louis?
What's good with you? Your sister
said you could handle this.
I got to set her straight?
So come on.
Keesen!
Let's go. Come on.
Me will come just now.
Let me grab something.
So. what do you got?
Yeah. so Agent
Lady. I was wrong.
Ain't nothing happening
tonight. I was wrong.
What do you mean
nothing's happening?
I messed up and I'm sorry.
And I can't do this.
What? Xavier. no. you can't just
- back out like this.
- I'm sorry. Agent Harmony...
- Xavier. you cannot...
- Hey!
You ready?
Me good.
Was that your guy?
Yeah. It was Xavier.
He said that
Washington Square Park
isn't happening tonight.
but it obviously is.
Just... give me a sec.
Yeah.
Hey. Manny...
Listen. I know you're with
your daughter tonight.
so I hope you even get this.
I also hope you actually think
that this is good news. but
I did go a little rogue.
And it was on my own
time. so don't worry.
but I actually did manage
to turn a cooperator... ish.
And that he said that there
was something happening
in Washington Square Park tonight.
But then he said there isn't.
Which makes me
think that there is.
And that it's bigger than
the whack-a-bum stuff
because why would they
be killing a vagrant
in Washington Square Park.
So. I feel like I should
definitely be there.
but I don't want to go
until I hear back from you
because I am trying
to be professional
and to respect
protocol. So. yeah.
when you get this. just hit me back
and yeah. I'll be sitting tight.
Okay. Bye.
So. are you gonna
wait for his approval
- or...
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Right.
Hey. Jared?
- Jared?
- Yeah.
The microwave's jammed.
The door won't open.
The microwave. Yeah. Yeah. It's
not jammed. It's a drawer now.
- It's a drawer?
- Yeah. You know. it's this whole thing.
There's a button.
Oh. my God.
Since your parents remodeled.
I can't figure out a damn thing
in this place. Are you
sure you're not hungry?
No. I'm not feeling too good.
I'm just gonna crash tonight.
Well. don't you have tutor?
I think I'm just gonna cancel.
If I'm sick. I don't
want to get Sarah sick.
- So... yeah.
- Did you call her?
I actually lost my phone. Do you
think you could call her for me?
Mom left her number on the
sheet next to the phone.
You do look a little flushed.
Okay. sweetie. I will.
- Thanks. Nanna.
- Can I get you some soup?
No. I'm just gonna go to bed.
- I'm not really hungry.
- All right.
- Well. hope you feel better.
- Yeah.
Oh. sweetheart. Love you.
- Love you too. Good night. Nanna.
- Good night.
Do you see her right there?
That's the tutor girl.
She gonna come. she gonna
post up on the building.
check her phone.
It's maybe Instagram or
something. I don't know.
But she waits. she
might call him. Hold on.
She ready. then they gonna go
across the park right
now and go to the Bean.
Do some school shit.
As soon she leaves with him.
that's when we go. okay?
What the fuck?
What the fuck!
Yo. I told Len to track him
the last two fucking Saturdays.
Wait. I got a backup.
I got these FedEx
joints. maybe we go.
- we knock on the door...
- Hey. Aked.
That him? Right
there. that door?
Yeah. that's him.
That's him. Where is he going? Where
is this motherfucker going? What?
That's a one-way. He
just went up a one-way.
Fuck. Go up next block.
Next block. Make a right.
I don't see shit.
Thought you said this man
was already there. chief?
No. I know. I know.
Okay. this right. right here. You take
this right. right here. Right here.
I just can't take anything
he says seriously.
All I can do is picture him sitting
in that chair with tin foil on.
That's not fair. Not
everyone can rock
- the silver fox like you.
- Oh. God bless you.
- but you know what I mean.
- Hi. Mom.
Hey. thanks for the heads up.
Yeah. Well. I hope you don't
mind the executive decision.
Yeah. yeah. yeah. No. I mean. no
sense doing tutor if he's sick.
- Night.
- Night. night.
- Good night. Kris.
- Good night. Derek.
I think he just
didn't wanna do tutor.
All right. Fuck it. Take
this left right here.
Right here. Right here.
- Right here?
- Yeah.
Nothing?
Fuck it. Fuck. Fuck. Fuck.
Wait. wait. wait. There's
he. There's he. Right there!
Yeah. Yes! Yeah. Keesen!
- Go. go. go. Xavier. Hurry. hurry. hurry!
- Hurry!
Hi. Thank you. You must
have my son's phone.
- He's always losing his stuff.
- Actually. we have your son.
- What?
- I said we have your son.
And we'll kill him if
you don't do what we say.
- Hang on. Hang on. Hang on.
- All right? Yo. lady.
- you're not in charge here.
- No. I said hang on!
You need to stop talkin
- and start listening...
- Sam?
Or this will be the worst night
of your life. You hear me?
What's going on?
- They have Jared.
- What?
Damn right. we do. And
here what's gonna happen...
Whoa. whoa. whoa. If this is a
joke. it's not funny. Who's talking?
Now. I'm gonna give you a figure.
and I suggest you write it down.
Do you have Jared? I
want to talk to Jared.
Who is this? Who is
talking to me right now?
Three hundred and fourteen thousand.
one hundred and fifty-nine.
- Wait. wait. wait. Just... wait.
- Write that number down. It's important.
- What are these numbers?
- One. four. one...
- This... This is money?
- Derek!
No. you need to tell us something.
Give us some information.
White sneakers. there's
writing on them.
Yellow and green
Trek mountain bike.
You're gonna get a call shortly
explaining where you pick
up the money. All right?
Yes. cash. Nothing bigger
than twenties. you hear me?
Man. I don't know. Why don't you
ask your fucking father-in-law
what his Atlantic City
credit limit is. All right?
Sure. about that move. Clarence?
You might want to rethink that.
Again. Sorry. Sorry.
Of course.
Sam. I am playing
chess with my friend...
Just... Sam. Slow down.
Slow down. Slow down!
What?
What!
I'm sorry. I...
I've got to go.
I'll... I'll...
Just tell him it's an emergency.
I need to borrow
against my credit limit.
Because I can't right now. Joey!
- Did she tell you anything?
- I know about as much as you do.
Look. just call Sey. If
he's not on the casino floor
then he's gonna be
awake somewhere.
Chef Jeff. Ms. McCusker.
you forgot to sign...
Not now. Bryce. Yes. Just do it.
Call me back.
- My God. Oh. my God.
- Sam. Anybody called?
Derek?
Joey called my guy
in Atlantic City.
They haven't told us a thing.
- You know. I'm sorry you're involved.
- What are you apologizing for?
Did you fucking do
it? Don't apologize.
- Wait. Joey?
- Wait. Dad! He said no police.
- Joey's not police. He's not anymore.
- I checked and he was there.
- Honest to God!
- He's the best there is.
- I checked and he was there.
- Kris!
- Yes?
- This is not about you.
- I know that. but I...
- Can we just take a beat?
- I looked in his room and he was there...
- We don't have a fucking beat.
- This is a nightmare.
- Kris?
- Kris.
- I would never... What?
- Kristen. it's not you.
- Yeah. I know.
- We're not mad at you.
- No. no. no. no. no. no.
- Mom! Mom!
- I'm fine. I'm fine.
Hey. Hey. hey.
Oh. my God.
I... I... can't. Okay. wait.
So. what? Police. Yes. or no?
Joey says... not until
Jared's safe at home.
And who the fuck knows about
my casino credit limit?
Fuck.
- Yes?
- Okay. listen to me.
There's a parking lot right
next to the south entrance
of the George Washington
Bridge. All right?
Tell your boys at the casino
to drop your cash there.
When you're on the
bridge with the money.
you'll receive your next
instruction. all right?
Look. if you're not
there by midnight.
if you're not alone or
police have been called.
your son will be killed.
Okay. put our son on the
phone. please. Put...
Fuck.
- Jared!
- What the fuck?
Jared? Oh. my God.
Where have you been?
Jeez. Mom. I just
went out for a walk.
- Calm down. What...
- Sweetheart.
- You lied to your grandmother.
- Derek. he's here.
- Derek. it's fine.
- No. no. no. no. no. no. no.
He was sneaking. He
lied to your mom and us.
I didn't realize
how late it was.
- I'm sorry.
- I'm so glad. I just...
- Please. Please just be honest with us.
- Stop. Fucking calm down.
Okay? Were you meeting someone?
A boy? A girl? It doesn't matter.
- Just talk to us. Please.
- This is not the time
to be fucking around. son.
This is not the time
to be fucking around.
- This is no time to fuck around.
- No. Dad. no.
Hold on. Just hold on.
Hey. you need to talk to
us. bud. What's going on?
Okay. you're not in trouble.
but this is important.
Jared.
There's this boy
I've been talking to.
He said he had all my stuff.
And he'd show it to me
if I went to go see him.
So. I lied to Nanna
and I snuck out.
When I got there he
was wearing my hoodie.
My original one from before I
replaced it. And he had my shoes too.
He really liked my bike. so I let
him ride it around a little bit.
But then a van came. these guys
jumped out and they threw him in.
And I couldn't do
anything about it.
I just got my bike
and I rode around
until I could work up the
nerve to come back home.
Oh. baby.
Oh. my God. That had
to have been horrible.
- I think they were after me.
- Why would you think that?
Well. if it had been two minutes
earlier. they would have gotten me.
Oh. baby.
Why would somebody be after me?
- We don't know.
- We don't know anything. bud.
What do you know about
this boy? What's his name?
His name is Nicky. Look.
is he gonna be okay?
Open it. Open it. Open
it right now. Open it.
Yeah. Come here. Come here.
Come here. Look at me.
Look at me. You know
how to take pills?
Did boss send you old man
gummy bear sleeping pills?
Shut the fuck up. I'm
not talking to you.
Jared. do you know
how to take pills?
Don't fuck with me. Look at these.
You know how to take these? Huh?
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Ruby. Here we go.
You're okay. You're good. Okay.
- Hey. Joey.
- Sam. Hello.
Hey. so the casino asked why
so much cash so quickly...
- So. you can cancel all that.
- He's here. Jared. He's in his room.
- Hey. Joey.
- How you doing. Mr. Browne?
He's... Jared's here?
- Well. that's good. Right?
- Oh. yeah.
Well. the place looks good. Wow.
Don't even recognize it.
What? What?
- Who is this?
- Derek.
Please. Who am I talking to?
Daddy? Dad?
- Who is this?
- Is there a problem?
No. sir. There's no problem. We just
need to gather some information.
Gather some information? What
the fuck are you talking about?
Gather some... What the
fuck are you talking...
Hello?
They're muting me?
Bolt cutters.
- Huh?
- Give me the bolt cutters.
Give me the fucking
bolt cutters.
Come here. Xavier. pull
over. Pull the fuck over.
Aked. what are you doing. buddy?
Record this right
now. Hurry. Hurry.
No. I do not negotiate
with a terrorist.
- Jeff. come on. They have someone's child.
- Okay. okay.
- So now. we call the police. Right?
- I don't know.
Do we call the police. Joey?
- Wait. is that them?
- Yeah. There's a video attached.
Play it.
- Oh. Holy Christ.
- Oh. my God!
Hold still. You're
making it worse. Jared.
Oh. Jesus Christ.
Oh. my God!
They think... they
think they have Jared.
- But they don't.
- Yeah. but if they find out they don't.
what's to keep them
from coming after him?
Well. what do we do?
Do we just pretend that
it's Jared or what?
Hello?
It hurts. Please
do what they say.
We just need a few more details.
Jared. I want you to
talk about yourself.
Call... Charisse.
We'll talk at midnight. If you're
on a bridge and if you're alone.
Wait. What... what
do you mean "alone?"
One person. No cops.
And if I don't have the
money by 1:11 a.m. sharp.
your boy. your grandson.
Chef Jeff. is dead.